### Adam Hart

Junior Full Stack Developer Vancouver, BC

LinkedIn: AdamHHart
Github: AdamHHart
www.adamhart.ca

adamhayhart@gmail.com

778-676-0676

I am a junior web developer with a passion for immersive tech. I come from a background of event and hospitality entrepreneurship. My love for creating quality, memorable customer experiences steered me into web development, and drives me to learn new dev tools, design, and build web apps.

1 year goals		5-10 year goals	
<ul><li>→ Join a quality dev team and company.</li><li>→ Build UIs with great user experiences.</li></ul>		<ul><li>→ Expert status in the immersive web.</li><li>→ Lead dev of innovative web experiences.</li></ul>	
Languages		Tools	
→ JavaScript, C#, SQL, HTML, CSS, Ruby		→ React, Express, Unity, NodeJS, Git, PostgreSQL, Jquery, MongoDB, Axios, Cypress, Jest	
<pre>Experience/Projects</pre>			
Nexposition Immersive Art Design, host, and experience immersive Gallery (ongoing) art and photo galleries online.		Unity (WebGL), C# Future:ShopifyAPI, webXR, AWS	
Interview Scheduler App	• • •		React, Axios, JSX, NodeJS, PostgreSQL, Jest, Storybook
Tapioca Loca	A restaurant ordering app.		Express, SQL, JS, HTML, CSS

# Work Experience

#### The Narcissus Cafe (Manager, Leaseholder)

Vancouver, B.C. - Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

On February 1st, 2020, I leased a struggling cafe in East Vancouver. With the vision to turn the business around, I found an opportunity for success through hosting dining, art, and music events. In February I increased revenue by 53% over the previous month. I hosted artists, chefs, and even the best Brazilian band in the city! In March, I saw the business sales channels closing up, breaking even until ultimately forfeiting the lease in December 2020.

The Gnocchi Nook (Owner, Head Chef)

Vancouver, B.C. - Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

Gnocchi Nook was a social dining events company that specialized in gnocchi, beer, and cocktails. We found cafes and breweries in the city that didn't offer dinner, and designed a menu and service style to match the space. The concept allowed us to test new recipes, kitchen designs, marketing strategies, and service techniques. 42 events, over 1000 dishes sold!

Green Leaf Brewing Co. (General Manager)

N. Vancouver, B.C. - Apr 2016 - Feb 2018

Managed all operations, significantly increasing revenues, staff retention, and customer loyalty over two years. Designed the kitchen and patio extension (43% capacity increase). Planned, promoted, and managed beer garden (doubled daily sales record) and other events. Created menu, training and operating procedures, and built supplier relationships.

# **Education**

Web Development Diploma
Bachelors in Geography, Business
IB High School Diploma

Lighthouse Labs 2021 University of Victoria, 2016 Mulgrave International School, 2012

### <u>Volunteer Experience</u>

<u>Volunteer Teacher's Assistant - Alcuin College</u>

North Vancouver, BC, Apr-Jun 2018

→ Supervised 15-20 grade 7/8s in PE, and grade 5/6s in Science, Humanities, and Art.

Vancouver Entrepreneurs Toastmasters Club

Vancouver, B.C. - Apr-Jun 2018

→ As Sergeant at Arms, I edit and upload videos, and manage club materials.